Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Unknown trumpet player performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1179; An unknown performer plays trumpet with Da Mixx.
  - Showtyme performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1180; Showtyme holds a microphone in his left hand while performing with Da Mixx. To the right fans are visible right up against the stage.
  - Sweet Cherie hosting Da Mixx and Rare Essence show at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1181; Sweet Cherie smiles and laughs while acting as host for the evening. She holds a microphone in her right hand and is surrounded by fans.
  - Da Mixx performing at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1182; Da Mixx members stand on stage reaching out toward the audience. Fans reaches back toward the band. The stage is sectioned off by a line of speakers.
  - Kool Kirky performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1183; Kool Kirky sits at a drums and plays cowbell while performing with Da Mixx.
  - Rare Essence performing at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1184; Rare Essence band members on stage during a show. The front line holds microphones, the back line includes trumpet and saxophone.
  - KeKe performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1185; KeKe holds a microphone in her right hand while performing with Rare Essence.
  - Da Mixx performing at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1186; From left to right Freaky Tye, 32, Showtyme, and Anthony Shields hold microphones and sing while performing with Da Mixx.
  - Sweet Cherie hosting Da Mixx and Rare Essence show at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1187; Sweet Cherie smiles and laughs acting as host for the evening. She holds a microphone in her right hand and is surrounded by fans.
  - 32, Sugar Rai, Showtyme, and Anthony Shields performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1188; From left to right 32, Sugar Rai, and Showtyme hold microphones and sign. To the far right Anthony Shields plays saxophone. Other performers are visible in the background.
  - 32, Sugar Rai, Showtyme, and Anthony Shields performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1189; From left to right 32, Sugar Rai, and Showtyme hold microphones and sign. To the far right Anthony Shields plays saxophone. Other performers are visible in the background.
  - 32 and Showtyme performing with Da Mixx at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1190; On stage from left to right Freaky Tye, 32, and Showtyme hold microphones and sign while performing with Da Mixx. Other performers playing keys and guitar are visible in the background. The left Killa Cal is seen looking on, a towel draped over his right shoulder. Fans is pressed right against the stage.
  - Fans at Da Mixx and Rare Essence show at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1191; Fans dance while attending Da Mixx and Rare Essence show.
  - Freaky Tye, 32, and Showtyme at Da Mixx and Rare Essence show at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1192; From left to right an Freaky Tye, 32, and Showtyme pose for the photographer. 32 holds a towel in his hands.
  - Jas. Funk and Go-Go Mickey performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1193; Jas. Funk appears to dance while Go-Go Mickey plays the congas while performing with Rare Essence.
  - Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and Derrick performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1194; From left to right Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and Derrick hold microphones and sing while performing with Rare Essence.
  - Jas. Funk performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1195; Jas. Funk stands at a microphone and signs while performing with Rare Essence.
  - Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and Whiteboy performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1196; Front left to right Shorty Corleone, KeKe, and Whiteboy stand at microphones and sing while performing with Rare Essence. Whiteboy is also playing guitar. Jas. Funk is just visible to the far right. In the background a horn line and drummer are visible.
  - Killa Cal and Shorty Corleone performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1197; From left to right Killa Cal and Shorty Corleone hold microphones and sing while performing with Rare Essence. Other performers and fans are visible in the background.
  - Killa Cal performing with Rare Essence at Four Points by Sheraton New Carrollton, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1198; Killa Cal stands with a hand on his face while performing with Rare Essence.
  - Maiesha performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at Sugar Bear's birthday party at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-07; 199chippy_1199; Maiesha holds a microphone in her left hand while performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at Sugar Bear's birthday party.
  - Cookie, Quisy, and D. Floyd on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern, 2012-05-14; 199chippy_1019; Cookie, on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern. Quisy and D. Floyd look on as Cookie adjusts her dress.
  - Cookie on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern, 2012-05-14; 199chippy_1020; Cookie celebrates her birthday on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern. Fans look on and smile as Cookie dances.
  - Cookie on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern, 2012-05-14; 199chippy_1021; From left to right D. Floyd, Ms Kim, and Cookie on stage with Still Familiar at Takoma Station Tavern. Fans smile.
  - Los performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0829; Los plays tambourine while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA 9 broadcast at 5 PM. A conga player is visible to the right.
  - Los performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0830; Los holds a microphone in his right hand and signs while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM. A cameraperson and crew are also visible.
  - Big G performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0831; Big G holds a microphone in his right hand while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0832; Weensey holds a microphone in his left hand and sings while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Big G and Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0833; From left to right Big G and Weensey sing while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Big G and Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0834; From left to right Big G and Weensey sing while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Big G performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0835; Big G performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Leslie Foster interviewing Big G during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0836; From left to right Big G is interviewed by journalist Leslie Foster while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM. A cameraperson is visible to the right.
  - Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0837; Weensey plays tambourine while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0838; Weensey plays tambourine while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Weensey performing with Backyard Band during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0839; Weensey holds a microphone in his left hand and sings while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Backyard Band with Susan Kennedy and Leslie Foster during a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0840; Some of the member of Backyard Band pose with Susan Kennedy and Leslie Foster while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM. Two children also pose with the group to the far left.
  - Big G with a journalist at a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0841; From left to right Big G poses with a journalist while performing with Backyard Band during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Child playing congas at a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0842; A child plays congas during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Rhea Williams and Big G at a WUSA9 broadcast, 2012-05-17; 199chippy_0843; Rhea Williams and Big G pose during the WUSA9 broadcast at 5 PM.
  - Shannon Browne at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1144; Shannon Browne holds up both hands in 'OK' signs. They are wearing a custom Chuck Brown memorabilia shirt that reads: 'Godfather of Go-Go, R. I. P. 8/22/36-5/16/12, Chuck Brown'.
  - KK makes a surprise appearance with Suttle Thoughts at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1145; KK holds a microphone to a fan during a surprise visit to La Fontaine Bleue two days after Chuck Brown's passing. An audience member kisses her right hand. She is performing with Suttle Thoughts. Kinjee and Chi-Ali can be seen in the background.
  - KK makes a surprise appearance with Suttle Thoughts at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1146; KK holds a microphone to a fan during a surprise visit to La Fontaine Bleue two days after Chuck Brown's passing. Three unidentified performers are to her left. Several other unidentified performers are also visible in the background.
  - KK makes a surprise appearance with Suttle Thoughts at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1147; KK holds a microphone and clasps a fan's hand during a surprise visit to La Fontaine Bleue two days after Chuck Brown's passing.
  - KK makes a surprise appearance with Suttle Thoughts at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1148; KK holds a microphone and clasps a fan's hand during a surprise visit to La Fontaine Bleue two days after Chuck Brown's passing. Several unidentified performers are visible to her left.
  - KK makes a surprise appearance with Suttle Thoughts at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1149; KK holds a microphone during a surprise visit to La Fontaine Bleue two days after Chuck Brown's passing.
  - Geronimo, Sweet Cherie, KK, Shannon Browne, and an unknown man at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1150; From left to right Geronimo, Sweet Cherie, KK, Shannon Browne, and an unknown man pose together. Sweet Cherie kisses KK on the cheek.
  - KK and Miss Loretta Sims at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1151; From left to right KK and Miss Loretta Sims smile at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sweet Cherie and KK at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1152; From left to right Sweet Cherie and KK smile and pose at La Fontaine Bleue following KK's surprise performance.
  - Shannon Browne, KK, and Mia Johnson at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-05-18; 199chippy_1153; From left to right Shannon Browne, KK, and Mia Johnson smile at La Fontaine Bleue following KK's surprise performance.
  - Vendor selling Chuck Brown t-shirts outside Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1001; A vendor holds up a t-shirt to that reads 'Chuck Brown Godfather of Go-Go' and features an image of Chuck Brown in the clouds surrounded by doves.
  - Vendor selling Chuck Brown t-shirts outside Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1002; A vendor holds up a t-shirt to that reads 'Chuck Brown Godfather of Go-Go' and features an image of Chuck Brown in the clouds surrounded by doves.
  - Sign and line control fences for Chuck Brown's viewing outside Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1003; Two people set up a large sign on a tripod. The sign has an image of Chuck Brown and reads 'the Godfather of Go-Go Chuck Brown Rest in Peace (August 22, 1936-May 16, 2012). In the background line control fencing is visible in front of the Howard Theatre.
  - Person holding a collage of Black musicians at Chuck Brown's viewing outside Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1004; A person hold a large collage image of Black musicians in front of the Howard Theatre.
  - Sign across from Howard Theatre on the day of Chuck Brown's viewing, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1005; A sign on a window reads ' Chucky Baby Don't Give A What???' with a hand drawn D. C. Flag. A person looking at a cell phone stands to the right.
  - Sign across from Howard Theatre on the day of Chuck Brown's viewing, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1006; A sign on a window reads ' Chucky Baby Don't Give A What???' with a hand drawn D. C. Flag. A person stands to the right.
  - People gathered for Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1007; A group of five people pose while waiting in like for Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre.
  - Sweet Cherie at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1008; Sweet Cherie arrives at the Howard Theatre for Chuck Brown's viewing. She pushes a baby stroller with a child. To the left a person ushers her in.
  - Councilman Kwame Brown arriving at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1009; Councilman Kwame Brown arrives for Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre. A person in a Chuck Brown tribute t-shirt holding a clipboard and keycard walks with Councilman Brown to the left.
  - Open coffin at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1010; Members of the public pay final respects to the open coffin of Chuck Brown at his viewing. People in suits flank the coffin. Mr. Brown's black hat is visible.
  - Lobby of Howard Theatre decorated for Chuck Brown's viewing, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1011; Signs, video slideshow, and flowers arranged in the lobby of Howard Theatre on the day of Chuck Brown's viewing.
  - Lobby of Howard Theatre decorated for Chuck Brown's viewing, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1012; Signs, video slideshow, and flowers arranged in the lobby of Howard Theatre on the day of Chuck Brown's viewing.
  - D. Floyd with journalists at Chuck Brow's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1013; D. Floyd speaks to a journalist and camera operator outside of Chuck Brown's viewing.
  - D. Floyd with journalists at Chuck Brow's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1014; D. Floyd speaks to a journalist and camera operator outside of Chuck Brown's viewing. Several news station trucks are visible in the background.
  - Rock Newman arriving at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1015; Rock Newman speaks with a police officer when arriving at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre. To the left the line to enter the Theatre is visible.
  - Vendor selling Chuck Brown t-shirts, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1016; A vendor sells t-shirts to that reads 'Chuck Brown Godfather of Go-Go' and features an image of Chuck Brown in the clouds surrounded by doves.
  - People in line for Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1017; People sit on folding chair or stand while waiting in line to enter Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre. One person holds up a framed piece of Chuck Brown art.
  - Bobby Smoot arriving at Chuck Brown's viewing at Howard Theatre, 2012-05-29; 199chippy_1018; Bobby Smoot arrives at the Howard Theatre for Chuck Brown's viewing. He wears a D. C. Metro bus operator uniform.
  - Street vendor sells memorabilia during Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0936; A street vendor smiles for a photograph. They appear to be selling Chuck Brown memorabilia prints outside of the Walter E. Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing.
  - Newspaper vendor sales memorabilia during Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0937; A newspaper vendor can be seen arranging newspapers to be sold at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. The vendor is wearing a Washington Post vest with Chuck Brown's image on the front.
  - Newspaper vendor sales memorabilia during Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0938; A newspaper vendor can be seen arranging newspapers to be sold at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. The vendor is wearing a Washington Post vest. The newspaper has an image of Chuck Brown on the cover.
  - Mourners lined up for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0939; People can be seen lined up outside of the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service. A person wearing a white dress and sunglasses stands in line, they hold a handkerchief toward their face.
  - Newspaper vendor sales memorabilia during Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0940; A newspaper vendor can be seen raising newspaper overhead to be sold at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. The vendor is wearing a Washington Post hat and vest. The newspaper has an image of Chuck Brown on the cover.
  - Mourner with Washington Post Chuck Brown memorabilia, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0941; A mourner smiles and presents their Washington Post newspaper memorabilia. The newspaper has Chuck Brown's image, and reads 'Style: the Godfather of Go-Go'.
  - Mourners dance outside the Walter E. Convention Center to celebrate the life of Chuck Brown, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0942; A mourner smiles while dancing outside of the Walter E. Washington Convention Center to celebrate the life of Chuck Brown. They are wearing a denim dress, disco ball earrings, and waving their hands in the air. Other Mourners can be seen dancing and standing around in the image.
  - Mourners on the escalators at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0943; Two people pose for a picture while riding the escalator at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center in attendance for Chuck Brown's homegoing service. They are both wearing custom printed Chuck Brown memorabilia shirts. The person on the right has exceptionally long fingernails.
  - Chuck Brown's homegoing service hosted at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0944; A digital billboard broadcasts an image of Chuck Brown to the attendees of his homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. The billboard reads 'Remembering Chuck Brown: the Godfather of Go-Go 1936-2012'.
  - Chuck Brown's casket at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0945; Chuck Brown's casket lay in the center of the Walter E. Washington Convention center. Fans and family can be seen in the image.
  - DJ Blakberri and Brad Clements at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0946; Brad Clements and partner De'Aun Evans pose while attending Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Go-Go Mickey and Ms. Miss Loretta at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0947; Go-Go Mickey and Miss Loretta Sims smile together while attending Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Miss Loretta Sims at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0948; Miss Loretta Sims smiles while attending Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. They are also wearing a custom memorabilia shirt that reads 'the Godfather of GoGo' stylized to look like the movie art from the film 1972 film 'the Godfather'.
  - Too Smooth at the Walter E. Washington Convention center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0949; Too Smooth smiles for a photograph, while attending Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Convention Center. He opens his arm to showcase his custom memorabilia shirt that reads 'In Memory of the Godfather of GoGo'.
  - Donnie Simpson speaking at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0950; Donnie Simpson addresses an audience gathered at the Walter E. Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service.
  - Mayor Marion Barry in attendance at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0951; Mayor Marion Barry sits and converses with another person at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center. He is wearing a pin with Chuck Brown's face on his lapel.
  - Howard Gospel Choir performs at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0952; The Howard Gospel Choir sing for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Reverend Tony Lee speaks at the Walter E. Washington Convention Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0953; Reverend Tony Lee speaks at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Mayor Marion Barry in attendance at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0954; Mayor Marion Barry reads a homegoing pamphlet at Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Sweet Cherie at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0955; Sweet Cherie smiles while attending Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Howard Gospel Choir performs at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0956; The Howard Gospel Choir sing for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Mighty Moe performing at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0957; Mighty Moe plays the congas during a performance for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Buggy performing at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0958; Buggy smiles while playing the drums for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Buggy performing at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center for Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0959; Buggy playing the drums for Chuck Brown's homegoing service at the Walter E. Washington Convention Center.
  - Mighty Moe and Donnie Simpson at Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0960; Mighty Moe and Donnie Simpson smile with each other at Chuck Brown's homegoing service.
  - Logan H. Westbrooks at Chuck Brown's homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0961; Logan H. Westbrooks at Chuck Brown's homegoing service.
  - Members of Chuck Brown's family attend his homegoing service, 2012-05-31; 199chippy_0962; Members of Chuck Brown's family at his homegoing service.